Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
- Washington Square Campus Buildings
  - Founders Monument - Gould Plaza
    - Gould Plaza, Students Reading and Chatting, April 1982; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6694; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 27)
    - Gould Memorial Plaza and Tisch Hall, Looking South, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6690; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 25)
    - President John M. Hester and Jerry Goldman Chairman of the Students Senators Council of the University Senate, Aerial View of Founders Monument, May 21, 1973; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6697; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 26)
      Hester, James M., 1924-2014; New York University. Washington Square Campus; New York University -- Buildings
    - President John M. Hester and Jerry Goldman, Chairman of the Student Senators Council of the University Senate with Founders Memorial Rededication Plaque, May 21, 1973; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6699 (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 27)
    - Construction of the Founders Monument in front of Tisch Building, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6850; Rodriguez, Robert F.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 28)
  - La Maison Francaise - Exterior
    - La Maison Francaise, Students Walking in Front of Building, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6701; Color Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - La Maison Francaise Sign, Student Standing in Front of Building, Summer Bulletin Picture, 1991; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6703; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - La Maison Francaise, 16 Washington Mews, New Sailors' Snug Harbor Property at Time of Photo, Looking South, circa 1946; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6705; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - La Maison Francaise, Looking West, April 26, 1957; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6707; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - La Maison Francaise, 16 Washington Mews, New Sailors' Snug Harbor Property at Time of Photo, Looking West, circa 1946; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6709; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - La Maison Francaise, Looking Southwest at East Side of University Place from Washington Mews, April 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6711; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - La Maison Francaise, Front Facade and Mews Entrance, January 16, 1969; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6713; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 7)
    - La Maison Francase, Artists Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6715; Color Print, (Photograph), 4x5 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 8)
    - Hostess, La Maison Francaise, Mrs. Ada Mordacques Squiers, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6717; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 9)
    - La Maison Francaise, Arthur Shatz, undated; Ua_PHOTO_001_ref6719; Shatz, Arthur; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 4x6 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 10)
    - La Maison Francaise, Doorway Entrance Close-up, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6721; Shatz, Arthur; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 11)
    - La Maison Francaise, Building Facade with Student Walking in Front, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6723; Shatz, Arthur; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 12)
    - La Maison Francaise, Washington Mews Arch and Front Facade, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6725; Forster, R; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 13)
    - La Maison Francaise, 2-4 1/2 University Place and 16 Washington Mews, West Side of University Place, circa 1946; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6727; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 14)
    - La Maison Francaise, Looking West with Buildings in Background, April 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6729; Simmons, William R.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 15)
    - La Maison Francaise Proposed Facade, Artists Rendering, circa 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6731; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 16)
    - La Maison Francaise, Old Front Door Close-up, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6733; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 17)
    - La Maison Francaise, Old Front Door and Facade, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6735; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 3 1/2x4 1/2 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 18)
    - La Maison Francaise, Old Front Door and Facade Illuminated, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6737; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 4 1/2x 3 1/2 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 19)
    - La Maison Francaise, Old Facade, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6739; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 20)
    - La Maison Francaise, Facade and Mews Archway, Looking Southwest, April 26, 1957; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6741; Gooen, Irwin; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 21)
    - La Maison Francaise, View From Building Across the Street, May 12, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6743; Seligson, Stanley; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 22)
    - La Maison Francaise, Reading Room with French Map, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6745; Shatz, Arthur; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 23)
  - La Maison Francaise - Events
    - Book Signing with Tom Bishop at La Maison Francaise, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6748; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 1)
      Bishop, Tom; New York University. Washington Square Campus; New York University -- Buildings
    - Reading of Beckett's Poetry and Prose at La Maison Francaise, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6750; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 4)
      Oliva, L. Jay (Lawrence Jay), 1933-2014; New York University. Washington Square Campus; New York University -- Buildings
    - Colloquium on Rural Life in Urban Society Today, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6752; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Mayor of Barcelona Speaking at La Maison Francaise, March 24, 1983; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6754; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 4)
    - Recital by Hugues Cuenod at La Maison Francaise Accompanied By David Noakes, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6756; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 5)
      Hugues, Cuenod; Noakes, David; New York University. Washington Square Campus; New York University -- Buildings
    - Lecture by Poet Francois Ponge at La maison Francaise, December 16, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6758; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 6)
      Ponge, Francois; New York University. Washington Square Campus; New York University -- Buildings
    - Fashion Show, La Maison Francaise, October 15, 1974; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6760; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 7)
    - Lecture by Composer and Conductor Pierre Boulez, February 23, 1972; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6762; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 8)
      Boulez, Pierre, 1925-; New York University. Washington Square Campus; New York University -- Buildings
  - La Maison Francaise - Interiors
    - La Maison Francaise Sitting Room with Stage, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6765; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 190, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - La Maison Francaise, Staircase Close-up, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6767; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - La Maison Francaise, Chandelier, 1986; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6769; Black and White print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 190, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - La Maison, Francaise, Fireplace and Mirror, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6771; Black and White print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 190, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - La Maison, Francaise, Tapestry, 1960; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6773; Black and White Print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 190, Folder 4, Item 5)
  - Fraternity Houses, 3-5 Washington Place
    - Fraternity Houses, Exterior, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6776; Black and White print (photograph), 3.5 x 5 inches (Box 190, Folder 5, Item 1)
      Fraternal organizations; Greek letter societies.; Student activities.; New York University. Washington Square Campus; New York University -- Buildings
    - Fraternity Houses, Interior, 1979; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6778; Black and White Print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 190, Folder 5, Item 2)
      Greek letter societies.; Fraternal organizations; New York University. Washington Square Campus; New York University -- Buildings
    - Fraternity Houses, New Dorm Spaces, 1983; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6780; Black and White Print (Photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 190, Folder 5, Item 3)
      Fraternal organizations; Greek letter societies.; New York University -- Buildings; New York University. Washington Square Campus
  - Galleria (Philip Johnson's Proposed Enclosure of Washington Sq. East, Model/Rendering and Presentations)
    - Galleria Proposal, Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6783; Black and White print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Galleria Proposal, Rendering, 1966; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6785; Black and White print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 2)
      Architectural drawings (visual works); New York University. Washington Square Campus; New York University -- Buildings
    - Galleria Proposal, Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6787; Black and White Print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Galleria Proposal, Arcade Rendering, 1968; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6789; Black and White print (Photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Galleria Proposal, Arcade Rendering, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6791; Black and White print (Photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Galleria Proposal, Arcade, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6793; Black and White print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 6)
      Architectural drawings (visual works); Architecture; New York University. Washington Square Campus; New York University -- Buildings
    - Galleria, Rendering, 1966; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6795; Black and White Print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Galleria, Rendering, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6797; Black and White Print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Galleria Arch, Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6799; Black and White print (Photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 9)
    - Galleria, Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6801; Checkman, Louis; Black and White print (Photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 10)
      Acculturation -- Brazil; Architecture; Architectural drawings (visual works); New York University. Washington Square Campus; New York University -- Buildings
    - Galleria Arch, Looking East, Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6805; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 11)
    - Galleria, Looking East, Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6807; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 12)
    - Galleria Facade, Looking Southeast, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6808; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 13)
    - Johnson and Foster Bulding Plans for Galleria Interior, Looking West, Rendering, May 15, 1968; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6811; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 14)
    - Philip Johnson's Plan for East and Southeast Sides of Washington Square, Showing Galleria, October 10, 1966; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6813; Checkman, Louis; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 15)
    - Galleria Looking Southeast, Rudolph Assocation Rendering, Feburary 1, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6803; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 16)
    - Galleria Looking West, Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6815; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 17)
    - Washington Square Park and Galleria, Looking South Southwest, November 12, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6817; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 18)
    - Galeria Arch, Looking Up at the Sky, Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6819; Checkman, Louis; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 19)
    - George A. Murphy, Samuel D. Leiderdorf, and Dr. James M. Hester (left to right), Looking down at Galleria Plans, November 12, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6821; Simmons, William R.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 20)
    - George A. Murphy, Samuel D. Leiderdorf, and Dr. James M. Hester, Examining Galleria Plans, November 12, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6823; Simmons, William R.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 21)
    - Alternate Galleria Plan, Looking East, Rendering, August 21, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6825; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 22)
    - Galeria Plan, Looking Southeast, Artist Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6827; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 23)
    - Savini Classico Risorante Milanese, Milano Galleria, Seen by Preident Hester, Postcard, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6829; Color (Print), Postcard, 4x6 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 24)
      Hester, James M., 1924-
    - Galleria Arch and Facade, Proposal, Rendering, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6831; Color Print, (Photograph), 7x9 (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 25)
  - General - Maps, Zoning, Models, Shadows, Multiple Buildings, Contact Sheets, and Unidentified Buildings
    - Map of New York University Campus and Greenwich Village, Rendering, Aerial, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6834; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Chan House - Fine Arts Building, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6836; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Faculty Club 22 Washington Square North, June 4, 1969; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6838; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - Singer Building, 561 Broadway, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6840; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - Map of Washington Square Center, Tentative Master Plan Study Prepared by the Office of the Director of Planning and Supervising Architect, UA_PHOTO_001_ref6842; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - Map of Washington Square Center, New York University Director of Plant and Properties, March 1966; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6844; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - Washington Square Campus Development Zoning, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6846; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 7)
    - Washington Square Park Traffic Study, August - September 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6848; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 8)
    - Number 35, NYU Buildings for Walking Tour Booklet, March 19, 1976; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6852; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 9)
    - Number 13, NYU Buildings for Walking Tour Booklet, March 19, 1976; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6854; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 10)
    - Number 40, NYU Buildings for Walking Tour Booklet, March 19, 1976; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6856; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 11)
    - Number 6, NYU Buildings for Walking Tour Booklet, March 19, 1976; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6858; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 12)
    - Number 19, NYU Buildings for Walking Tour Booklet, March 19, 1976; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6860; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 13)
    - Chan House Looking South, June 9, 1983; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6862; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 14)
    - 707 Broadway, View from Mercer, May 2, 1970; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6864; Arnold, Katz; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 15)
    - Washington Mews, Closeup of Lights on Doorway, April 1969; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6866; Seligson, Stanley; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 16)
    - Green Street, Looking North, April 1969; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6868; Seligson, Stanley; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 17)
    - Greene Street, Looking South, April 1969; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6870; Seligson, Stanley; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 18)
  - Gallery of Living Art
    - The Museum of Living Art at NYU from 1927-1939, undated; cuid17570; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - The Museum of Living Art at NYU from 1927-1939, Closeup, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6875; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Hayden Hall Construction
    - Hayden Hall Entrance, 33 Washington Square West, Looking West, Undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6897; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Hayden Cafeteria, Room Full of Students, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6899; M.E., Warren; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Hayden Dining Hall, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6901; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Hayden Cafeteria, Table of Students in Discussion, 1967; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6903; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Hayden Hall Dining Room, Students in Discussion, 1967; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6905; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Hayden Hall, Fountain with Statue, May 14, 1985; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6907; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Hayden Hall, View From Washington Square Park, Looking Northwest, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6909; Color Print, (Photograph), 6x7 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Hayden Hall, View from Washington Square Park Through Trees, Looking West, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6911; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Hayden Hall, NYU School of Law, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6913; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 9)
    - Hayden Hall, View from Washington Square Park in the Snow, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6915; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Hayden Hall and Washington Square Park, Looking West, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6917; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 11)
    - Hayden Hall, Entrance Facade Close-up, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6919; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 12)
    - Hayden Residence Hall, New York University Law Center, Artist Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_ref6921; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 13)
      Eggers & Higgins; New York University. Washington Square Campus; New York University -- Buildings
    - Hayden Hall Construction Site, Building Facade and Cars, March 16, 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6923; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches
      William A. Berbusse, Jr. Inc.; Eggers & Higgins; New York University. Washington Square Campus; New York University -- Buildings
    - Hayden Hall Construction Site, South Elevation, Front, March 16, 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6925; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 14)
    - Hayden Hall Construction Site, South Elevation, Rear, March 16, 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6926; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 15)
    - Hayden Hall Construction Site, North Elevation, Rear, March 16, 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6928; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 16)
    - Hayden Hall Construction Site, South Wall with Ladders, April 30, 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6930; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 17)
    - Hayden Hall Construction Site, North West, Rear, April 30, 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6932; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 18)
    - Hayden Hall Construction Site, Southwest, Rear, April 30, 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6935; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 19)
    - Hayden Hall Construction Site, Front Wall, June 30, 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6937; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 20)
    - Hayden Hall Construction Site, South Wall with Scaffolding, June 30, 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6939; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 21)
    - Hayden Hall Construction Site, Rear Wall, June 30, 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6941; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 22)
      Eggers & Higgins; William A. Berbusse, Jr. Inc.; New York University. Washington Square Campus; New York University -- Buildings
    - Hayden Hall Construction Site, Filter Pit, July 31, 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6943; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 23)
    - Hayden Hall Construction Site, Looking West, July 31, 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6945; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 24)
    - Hayden Hall Construction Site, Swimming Pool, July 31, 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6947; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 25)
    - Hayden Hall Construction Site, Looking Southeast, September 1, 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6949; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 26)
    - Hayden Hall Construction Site, Filter Pit, Looking Southwest, September 1, 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6951; Black and While Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 27)
    - Hayden Hall Construction Site, Pit with Workers, Looking West, September 1, 1955; UA_PHOTO_ref6953; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 28)
    - Hayden Hall Construction Site, Looking West, September 30, 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6955; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 29)
      William A. Berbusse, Jr. Inc.; Eggers & Higgins
    - Hayden Hall Construction Site, Looking South, September 30, 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6957; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 30)
      Eggers & Higgins; William A. Berbusse, Jr. Inc.
    - Hayden Hall Construction Site, Looking East, September 30, 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6959; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 1, Item 31)
    - Exterior, Interior, Construction, Re-dedication, cuid17966 (Box 230, Box 231)
  - Ireland House
    - Ireland House, Looking East, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6962; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Ireland House, Artist Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6964; Zigler, Jane; Color Print, (Drawing), 8x10 inches (Box 192, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Ireland House, Color Photograph, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6966; Color Print, (Photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 192, Folder 2, Item 3)